Tzvi Hamerman

SUMMARY

I'm a software engineer with experience developing applications in the Javascript ecosystem and am comfortable with various cloud technologies. I recently built Aria, an open source, self-hosted tool that enables canary deployment and analysis in a few simple steps.

EXPERIENCE

Aria, Co-Creator, Software Engineer

2021 - present

- Co-Created Aria, a self-hosted, "quick-start" framework that enables canary deployment and analysis in existing AWS environments.
- Designed, prototyped, and built Aria using Amazon Web Services (EC2, ALB, S3, IAM).
- Led Aria CDK development that enables developers to easily insert and teardown canary infrastructure in existing production environments (Node, TypeScript, CDK, SDK, CloudFormation).
- Implemented a dashboard UI for Aria setup, infrastructure deployment, and teardown (Svelte, TailwindCSS).
- Configured Aria monitoring and analysis toolkit: (Prometheus, Kayenta, Referee, and Grafana).
- Produced animations and diagrams for Aria demos, case study website, and presentation.
- Co-authored technical case study and technical presentation (aria-deploy.github.io 🗷).

Self-employed, Full Stack Web Developer

2019 - 2021

- Developed open-source software with technologies such as React, Express, Node, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Docker, HTML, and CSS.
- RequestBucket RequestBin-like database-backed application for receiving and debugging webhooks in real time (Express, MongoDB, React, Tailwind, SSE, Docker).
- TrelloClone A Trello-like collaboration app (MongoDB, Node, Express, React/Redux).

Apex-Ventures, Purchaser, Operations Specialist

2013 - 2019

• Managed daily operations, warehouse, customer-service, shipping/receiving, for New York based online retailer.

SKILLS

Languages and Frameworks

Javascript (ES6), Go, Node, Express, React, Redux, Handlebars, SQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Tailwind

Cloud

AWS (EC2, ALB, IAM, S3, CDK, SDK, CloudFormation), Digital Ocean, Docker, Heroku

Web

HTTP, REST, APIs, Git / Github, HTML, CSS, DOM

EDUCATION

Launch School 2019 – 2021

Multi-year mastery-based software engineering program

B.S. Judaic Studies, Excelsior College

2019